streetcheck.co.uk 2019-07-30

# Our Privacy Policy

**Last Updated: 8 th March 2018**

Wired Software Ltd ("us", "we", or "our") operates StreetCheck (the "Site", "www.StreetCheck.co.uk"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. 

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions. 

## Information Collection and Use

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address and telephone number ("Personal Information"). 

## Information Storage

We store your data in U.K. datacentres, hosted by Microsoft Azure. If you are a StreetCheck API user, we may store a copy of your contact data with our accounting provider E-Crunch Ltd for the purposes of billing and invoicing - you can view their privacy policy [on the Crunch website](https://signup.crunch.co.uk/signup/privacypolicy.xhtml). 

We maintain strict security standards and procedures with a view to preventing unauthorised access to your Personal Information. We use leading technologies such as (but not limited to) data encryption, server authentication, user profiles and passwords to protect the security of your data. 

## Log Data

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. 

## Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site. More information and options for changing your cookie preferences can be found on our Cookie Policy page. 

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

## Links to Other Sites

Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third-party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. 

We may on occasion display affiliate links to other websites. Should you click on these links, and subsequently purchase the product (for instance a broadband package), StreetCheck will receive a payment from that website for referring you. We will only create these links where we believe that the product is truly one that our customers would want, and we use this money to run the website. 

Wired Software Ltd has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services. 

## Data Controller

StreetCheck is a trading name of Wired Software Ltd, which is a data controller registered with the Information Commissioner's Office. The registration number is ZA260603, and our record can be check on the [ICO website](https://ico.org.uk/register). 

## Accessing Your Data

You may download a copy of the data that StreetCheck holds about you at any time by logging in and visiting your account details page. 

If you do not have an account but have signed up for email alerts from us, then you can request this data by using our contact page to send us a request to export your data. Please remember to include your email address.

## Deleting Your Data

If you have previously registered on our site, and now wish to delete your account, you may do so by visiting your account details page, and following the instructions at the bottom of that page. Doing so will completely erase your records from our website. 

If you do not have an account but have signed up for email alerts from us, then you can remove this data by either using the "Unsubscribe" link in any email received, or by using our contact page to send us a request to delete your data. Please remember to include your email address.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

Wired Software Ltd may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
